<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>(DEMO) InVerse/MOD - Teegro Update</name>
    <directory>inverse</directory>
    <id>2810781873</id>
    <description>[b]InVerse mod includes 3 new characters for now:[/b]

[h1]Dream[/h1]

[b]Quick note:[/b] PLEASE do not confuse her with other &quot;Dreams&quot; of this world. The character is fully original. Thank you!

Keep yourself safe with her passive [b]&quot;Dream's Dream Book&quot;[/b] that can restore health and give soul hearts. But to be able to do that, you need find special rooms that give charges to the bood depending on how rare they are.

Additionally, Dream has a starting [b]&quot;Momentuum&quot;[/b] - powerful item that can do almost anything depending on where you throw it. Also, you can craft [b]&quot;Momentuum Cards&quot;[/b] with it if you have any tartot cards in hand, we recommend you give them a try!

[h1]Tainted Dream[/h1]

Balance between life and death with her pocket [b]&quot;Pilfer&quot;[/b] item that can give you health. But more you have - more chances to leave you with a half a heart instead. And don't try to ignore it too. Your health melts so no HP up is permanent.

While at half a heart, t.Dream takes her lost form, granting most of the Lost abilities and better stats.

[b]Warning![/b] The character isn't fully implemented and will be fully reworked in future updates![/i]

[h1]Teegro[/h1]

The newest addition to InVerse mod. Acts more like &quot;challenge&quot; character. For him, most of the items locked behind the [b]Hunter Locks[/b] (even items you leave behind, so be careful). To unlock them, collect [b]Hunter Key Parts[/b] to get a full [b]Hunter Key[/b]. There are many ways to get them but most reliable one is to complete rooms without taking damage.

More skill = more items, but besides that Teegro has some unique passives that help him with gameplay like guaranteed drops or better deals.

[h1]Plans[/h1]

&gt; For now we're planning adding a few new characters as well as finally adding new items and challenges but it can take some time so stay tuned!

[h1] Special Thanks [/h1]

[list]
    [*]KOSMOGOR - all the coding.
    [*]SGT-X - Character portraits sketches.
    [*]Sanio - Just a cool guy.
[/list]</description>
    <version>1.4</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Trinkets"/>
    <tag id="Cards"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Sound Effects"/>
</metadata>
